stanwinstonschool.com 2017-05-01

# Privacy Policy | Stan Winston School of Character Arts

## **Privacy and Our Privacy Policy**

We absolutely value your privacy. When you visit our website, email us, call us, or make purchases, we may collect certain personal information such as your name, mailing address, phone number, and email address. We may also collect information related to purchases such as dates of purchase, the product purchased and serial number, as well as credit card information. We also may collect information so that we may better serve all of our visitors. Such information may include reasons why you are interested in our services and products, your level of education, your occupation, and how we can deliver the best experience for you.

The Stan Winston School website uses cookies, tracking pixels and related technologies. Cookies are small data files that are served by our platform and stored on your device. Our site uses cookies dropped by us or third parties requested by us, for a variety of purposes including to operate and personalize the website. Cookies may also be used to track how you use the site in order to target ads of potential interest to you on other websites.

We maintain policies and procedures to safeguard any information collected. We do not make any collected information available to unrelated third parties for sale, rent, or for free, without your consent. However, we are required to provide certain information to specific businesses that assist our customer service in areas including the taking and fulfillment of orders, the financial details of credit card orders, the receipt and assessment of customer feedback, and the handling of shipping and delivery. Disclosure of collected information may also be required by subpoena, court order, or other valid legal process from any authorized government agency or Court. 

User feedback is not confidential, and may be shared with others.  Also, we cannot guarantee that any transmissions may or will not be intercepted or hacked by third parties, whether or not encryption is used. 

Notwithstanding the foregoing, we reserve the right to disclose or reveal all or part of any of your personal information if required in connection with any investigation, claim or complaint arising out of your use of the website, or to protect the rights, safety and/or welfare of us, other users, and the public at large. We also reserve the right to disclose or reveal any personal information that we believe to be necessary to comply with any applicable law, response to legal process, or valid request by a governmental agency.

It is your responsibility to notify us immediately if you become aware of any unauthorized use of your account or other security breach.
